<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Adhesive</string>
    <string name="loginmenu_Welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="loginmenu_Desc">Welcome to adhesive, where all brands have stories to tell</string>
    <string name="loginmenu_loginbutton">Login Here &lt;</string>
    <string name="loginmenu_registerbutton">Register Here ></string>
    <string name="loginmenu_loginbutton_desc">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="loginmenu_registerbutton_desc">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="login_Title">Login</string>    <string name="login_Desc">Login using your credentials below</string>
    <string name="login_emailHint" translatable="false">Email</string>
    <string name="login_passwordHint" translatable="false">Password</string>
    <string name="login_problems">Having problems loging in?</string>
    <string name="login_donthaveaccount">Dont have an Account?</string>
    <string name="register_title">Register</string>
    <string name="register_desc">Register using the fields below:</string>
    <string name="register_name">Name</string>
    <string name="register_Email" translatable="false">Email</string>
    <string name="register_Password" translatable="false">Password</string>
    <string name="register_sex_male">Male</string>
    <string name="register_sex_feminine">Feminine</string>
    <string name="register_datanascimento">Birthday</string>
    <string name="register_registerbutton">Register!</string>
    <string name="register_alreadyhaveaccount">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="login_problems_button">Click Here</string>
    <string name="login_missingfields_title">Empty fields detected</string>
    <string name="login_missingfields_message">Check your email / password for blank fields and try again.</string>
    <string name="login_missingfield_positive">Close</string>
    <string name="login_wrongPasswordEmail_Message">Wrong Password/Email try again</string>
    <string name="login_wrongPasswordEmail_Title">Error Loging in</string>
    <string name="login_wrongPasswordEmail_Postive" translatable="false">Ok!</string>
    <string name="login_loadingpopup_title">Log In!</string>
    <string name="login_loadingpopup_message">Please waiting, check credentials</string>
    <string name="register_dialogmissingitems_title">Empty Fields detected</string>
    <string name="register_dialogmissingitems_message">Check for empty fields and try again.</string>
    <string name="register_dialogmissingitems_positive" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="register_progressTitle">Registering…</string>
    <string name="register_progressMessage">Creating Account</string>
    <string name="register_failed_title">Error Registering</string>
    <string name="register_failed_message">Error Creating Account, check details and try again</string>
    <string name="register_failed_positive" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_4">No Network</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_4">Check you internet connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_4" translatable="false">Ok!</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_1">Missing Fields</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_1">Check for missing fields and try again</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_1" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_2">Incorrect Email</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_2">Your Email is incorrect try again</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_2" translatable="false">Ok!</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_7">Email already in use</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_7">Email already in use, login or recover your acount in the login screen</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_7" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="menu_main_initial">Home</string>
    <string name="main_menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="main_menu_contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="main_menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" translatable="false">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_8">No user found</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_8">No user found with that email,check your email and try again</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_8" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_3">Server Error</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_3">Server Encountered an error, try again later</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_3" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_6">Invalid Password</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_6">Password Doesn\'t macth with our records, try again</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_6" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_5">Invalid Session</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_5">Your Session token was invalid,or logged in on another device, log in again,</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_5" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="fragment_home_text_1">"We are a Branding + Digital studio that works, in close proximity to partners, companies and consumers, brands that communicate stories with soul and in personalized printed and digital experiences. "</string>
    <string name="fragment_home_text_2">It is formed by a passionate and attentive team, adjustable to the objectives and budget of each project, working in different business sectors and demographic contexts.</string>
    <string name="settings_account_title">Account</string>
    <string name="settings_account_changepersonaldata">Change Email</string>
    <string name="settings_account_changePassword">Change Password</string>
    <string name="settings_account_logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="settings_account_deactivate">Deactivate Account</string>
    <string name="settings_application_title">Application</string>
    <string name="settings_application_theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="settings_legal_title">Legal Information</string>
    <string name="settings_legal_OpenSourceLicenses">Open Souce Licenses</string>
    <string name="settings_legal_closedsource">Closed Source Licenses</string>
    <string name="settings_legal_privacy">Privacy statement</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_13">LogOut Failed</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_13">Error loggin you out, try again,</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_13" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_logout_title">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="dialog_logout_message">Are you sure you want to logout?</string>
    <string name="dialog_logout_positive">Yes</string>
    <string name="dialog_logout_negative">No</string>
    <string name="gallery_project1_title" translatable="false">C.M Do Barreiro</string>
    <string name="gallery_project1_Message">Creation of brand and corporate identity, creative concept and graphic image of campaign, graphic design of communication pieces and merchandising to support campaigns, creation of online presence of the event</string>
    <string name="gallery_moreinfo">More Info +</string>
    <string name="gallery_project2_title" translatable="false">Grupo Medinfar</string>
    <string name="gallery_project2_message">UX Design and implementation of E-detailings for medical information delegates</string>
    <string name="gallery_project3_title" translatable="false">Herdade Dos Outeiros Altos</string>
    <string name="gallery_project3_message">Brand creation, institutional communication, wine label design and online brand presence.</string>
    <string name="gallery_project4_title" translatable="false">Progenie Engineering</string>
    <string name="gallery_project4_message">Brand redesign, creation of institutional communication and online brand presence.</string>
    <string name="gallery_project5_title" translatable="false">Grupo Medinfar</string>
    <string name="gallery_project5_message">Brand creation and label design</string>
    <string name="logout_title">Log Out</string>
    <string name="logout_message">Logging you out, please wait…</string>
    <string name="gallery_client">Client:</string>
    <string name="gallery_project">Project:</string>
    <string name="gallery_Services">Services:</string>
    <string name="gallery_project1_services">Brand Design &amp; Strategy, Print Design, Interactive Design &amp; Social Media</string>
    <string name="gallery_project2_services">UX Design, Mobile Application Implementation</string>
    <string name="gallery_project3_services" translatable="false">Brand Design, Print Design, Package Design, UX Design, Desktop + Mobile Implementation, Content Management System, Social Media</string>
    <string name="gallery_project4_services" translatable="false">Brand Design, Print Design, UX Design, Desktop + Mobile Implementation, SEO Consulting, Content Management System, Social Media</string>
    <string name="gallery_project5_services" translatable="false">Brand Design &amp; Package Design</string>
    <string name="gallery_projectDetails">Project details</string>
    <string name="gallery_projectGallery">Project Gallery</string>
    <string name="settings_legal_userAgreement">End User License</string>
    <string name="UserAgreementMessage" translatable="false">End-User License Agreement (EULA) of Adhesive \n This End-User License Agreement (\"EULA\") is a legal agreement between you and Adhesive\n This EULA agreement governs your acquisition and use of our Adhesive software (\"Software\") directly from Adhesive or indirectly through a Adhesive authorized reseller or distributor (a \"Reseller\").\n Please read this EULA agreement carefully before completing the installation process and using the Adhesive software. It provides a license to use the Adhesive software and contains warranty information and liability disclaimers.\n This EULA agreement shall apply only to the Software supplied by Adhesive herewith regardless of whether other software is referred to or described herein. The terms also apply to any Adhesive updates, supplements, Internet-based services, and support services for the Software, unless other terms accompany those items on delivery. If so, those terms apply.\n\n License Grant\n \tAdhesive hereby grants you a personal, non-transferable, non-exclusive licence to use the Adhesive software on your devices in accordance with the terms of this EULA agreement.\n \tYou are permitted to load the Adhesive software (for example a PC, laptop, mobile or tablet) under your control. You are responsible for ensuring your device meets the minimum requirements of the Adhesive software.\n \tYou are not permitted to:\n \t\tEdit, alter, modify, adapt, translate or otherwise change the whole or any part of the Software nor permit the whole or any part of the Software to be combined with or become incorporated in any other software, nor decompile, disassemble or reverse engineer the Software or attempt to do any such things \t\tReproduce, copy, distribute, resell or otherwise use the Software for any commercial purpose \t\tAllow any third party to use the Software on behalf of or for the benefit of any third party \t\tUse the Software in any way which breaches any applicable local, national or international law \t\tuse the Software for any purpose that Adhesive considers is a breach of this EULA agreement</string>
    <string name="UserAgreementTitle">End User License</string>
    <string name="UserAgreementPositive" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="PrivacyStatementTitle">Privacy Statement</string>
    <string name="PrivacyStatementMessage" translatable="false">Privacy Policy Adhesive built the Adhesive app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Adhesive at no cost and is intended for use as is.  This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.  If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. we will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.  The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Adhesive unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.  Information Collection and Use  For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to Email. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.  The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.  Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app  Google Play Services Log Data  we want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.  Cookies  Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device\'s internal memory.  This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.  Service Providers  we may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:  To facilitate our Service; To provide the Service on our behalf; To perform Service-related services; or To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. we want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.  Security  we value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  Links to Other Sites  This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. we have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.  Children’s Privacy  These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.  Changes to This Privacy Policy  we may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. we will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.  This policy is effective as of 2020-05-13  Contact Us  If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at joaogouveia143@gmail.com.</string>
    <string name="PrivacyStatementPositive" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="ClosedSourceLicensesTitle">Closed Source Licenses</string>
    <string name="ClosedSourceLicensesMessage" translatable="false">No Closed Source APIs / external tool was used</string>
    <string name="ClosedSourceLicensePositive" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="OpenSourceLicensesTitle">Open Source Licenses</string>
    <string name="OpenSourceLicensesMessage" translatable="false">Google Play Services https://developers.google.com/   Android image slider\\n\\n Copyright [2019] [Ali Hosseini]\\n Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0; you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\\n \\t\\thttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\\n Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.\\n</string>
    <string name="OpenSourceLicensesPositive" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_18">Error Sending Message</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_18">Error sending message, try again later.</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_18" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_19">Message sent</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_19">Message Sent Successfully</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_19" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="sendmessage_loadinTittle">sending message</string>
    <string name="sendmessage_loadinMessage">sending message, please wait</string>
    <string name="permission_call_error">Permission to make phone calls denyed</string>
    <string name="call1" translatable="false">927878000</string>
    <string name="call2" translatable="false">927878000</string>
    <string name="call3" translatable="false">927878000</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_21">Error changing Password</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_21">Error Changing Password, try again</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_21" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_22">Password Changed Successfully</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_22">Password Changed Successfully</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_22" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="changepassword_dialog">Change Password</string>
    <string name="changepassword_dialog_Message">Changing your password, please wait</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_23">Email Changed</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_23">Email Changed Successfully</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_23" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_24">Error changing Email</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_24" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_24">Error changing your email try again later</string>
    <string name="dialog_Email">Change Email</string>
    <string name="dialog_Email_Message">Changing your email, please wait</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_25">Account Deactivated</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_25">Account Deactivated Successfully, to reactivate the account you will need to register again</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_25" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Title_26">Error Deactivating Account</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Message_26">Error deactivating Account, try again later</string>
    <string name="dialog_error_Positive_26" translatable="false">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_deactivatingtitle">Deactivating Account</string>
    <string name="dialog_deactivatingmessage">Deactivating Account, please wait</string>
    <string name="contacts_cardview">" Talk to us:"</string>
    <string name="contacts_name1">" Subject Matter:"</string>
    <string name="contacts_name2">Message:</string>
    <string name="contacts_EditText">Text</string>
    <string name="contacts_button_Send">Send</string>
    <string name="contacts_title">Contacts:</string>
    <string name="Contacts_Call">Call</string>
    <string name="contacts_CardView2">Adress:</string>
    <string name="Settings_NewPassword">Insert New Password</string>
    <string name="Settings_NewEmail">Insert New Email</string>
    <string name="Cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="Accept_ok" translatable="false">OK</string>
    <string name="deactivte_title">Deactivate Account?</string>
    <string name="deativate_message">Please Confirm this action</string>
    <string name="deactivate_positive">Yes</string>
    <string name="deactivate_negatove">No</string>
    <string name="retrun" translatable="false">&lt;</string>
</resources>
